Hi and welcome to my channel! I always wanted to say this because everyone on YouTube seems to say this like
Hi, welcome to my channel! Hi! Whatever!
No, but I had the idea to record some videos because there have been a lot of questions concerning my outfits
and different types of materials and what my wardrobe looks like and stuff like that.
And so I thought about doing some small clips and uploading them to, I don't know yet to be honest, Instagram, YouTube, I'll see.
So the initial thought was to do another question and answer video about this dress by Lida Pohl
because it's latex. There have been a lot of questions concerning this material, how to
maintain it, how to care for it, how to wear it.
I asked Glitterpool to help me out with a few questions and I'll tell you about
their answers now.
Okay, so on the outside it's latex basically and on the inside it's pretty elastic fabric like, I don't know, yoga pants or sport pants.
and it's really smooth and you can stretch it.
So...
I don't want to break it.
Lidapol said that the latex is not supposed to detach from the fabric
but you should take care of it like you do with your latex clothing
and you should order it in the size you actually wear and not smaller.
So if you want it to look good, order it in your size
and once you wear it it won't look different than latex but it has a
different feeling on the inside.
Some of you asked if you can buy this as sheet material and I asked the
manufacturer and they said that you should write an email directly to them
and they'll help you out and give you further information. One of the main
questions was about the shiner I used. This came with a dress. You can basically
just use your latex shiner as well. Whatever product you use just take care
of it like of your latex clothing so to say. So if you want to wash your dress
you can use your normal latex products as well. I washed this dress once so far
and I put it in warm water. I washed it by hand. I put a few drops of silicone oil
into the water and just let it dry afterwards.
And of course if you're a real latex fan and latex fetishist this is probably not
going to satisfy your needs or whatever because it is fabric on the inside. So
it's really good to just put on really quick, put on like I don't know every day
and you can't compare to 100% latex because it's fabric on the inside but
nevertheless it's really cool and it's really fast to put on. So it's not a
replacement for latex but an addition at least for me. Datex not latex.
Thank you.